Organized, collaborative, and highly skilled iOS developer with 6+ years of professional experience in dynamic and deadline-driven work environments. Eager to join BrambleSoft to delight its customers with magical experiences. In previous roles developed 10+ iOS apps that were downloaded over 700K times, and earned featured mentions in the App

Professional Experience

United States FlyBy Technologies, Los Angeles, CA| March 2013 - June 2016

- Performed technical designs and implementation of 10+ complex iOS apps.
- · Reviewed client requirements, wireframes, and designs for technical feasibility.
- · Collaborated with the scrum team to translate client requirements into implementable user stories.
- · Improved product quality through code reviews, writing effective unit tests and collaborating with QA on implementing automation testing

Key achievement:

- Developed and launched apps in over 50+ countries that earned featured mentions in the App Store.
- · Achieved over 500K downloads on the App Store.

Uzbekistan NAPA Automative | April 2019 - November 2021

- Worked closely with product managers and designers to define a rich Full stack experience for the user.
- · Supported the architect in improving base site.
- Explored new technologies and shared findings with the team.
- Supported and streamlined company policies, procedures, mission, and standards of ethics and integrity.
- Led the discovery phase of medium to large projects to come up with a high-level design.

Education

Bachelor's degree in Computer engineering Tashkent university of information technology at Tashkent | April 2010 - April 2014

Key Skills

- React Native
- Android/IOS
- Full stack
- PHP(CI, Laravel, Wordpress)
- Reactjs